const menuCat = {
  team: `
        <div class="create-monster-container">
            <div class="plus" data-monster="0"><img src="/img/plus.svg" alt="add monster"></div>
            <div class="plus" data-monster="1"><img src="/img/plus.svg" alt="add monster"></div>
            <div class="plus" data-monster="2"><img src="/img/plus.svg" alt="add monster"></div>
            <div class="plus" data-monster="3"><img src="/img/plus.svg" alt="add monster"></div>
        </div>
        `,
  fight: `
       <div class="challengers-icon"> </div>
    `,
  shop: `
        <h1>SHOP
    `,
  quest: `
        <h1>QUEST
    `,
};

const monsterDex = {
  bugMonster: {
    1: { front: "bug-front", back: "bug-back" },
    2: { front: "bigbug-front", back: "bigbug-back" },
  },
  birdMonster: {
    1: { front: "bird-front", back: "bird-back" },
  },
  capyMonster: {
    1: { front: "capy-front", back: "capy-back" },
  },
  catMonster: {
    1: { front: "cat-front", back: "cat-back" },
    2: { front: "occelot-front", back: "occelot-back" },
    3: { front: "lion-front", back: "lion-back" },
  },
  cerfMonster: {
    1: { front: "cerf-front", back: "cerf-back" },
  },
  doMonster: {
    1: { front: "do-front", back: "do-back" },
    2: { front: "dofin-front", back: "dofin-back" },
    3: { front: "mermaid-front", back: "mermaid-back" },
  },
  pingoMonster: {
    1: { front: "pingo-front", back: "pingo-back" },
    2: { front: "pingolin-front", back: "pingolin-back" },
    3: { front: "dino-front", back: "dino-back" },
  },
  sleepyMonster: {
    1: { front: "sleepy-front", back: "sleepy-back" },
  },
  snakeMonster: {
    1: { front: "snake-front", back: "snake-back" },
  },
  fairyMonster: {
    1: { front: "fairy-front", back: "fairy-back" },
    2: { front: "mage-front", back: "bigfairy-back" },
  },
  pomMonster: {
    1: { front: "pom-front", back: "pom-back" },
    2: { front: "pomking-front", back: "pomking-back" },
  },
  gossMonster: {
    1: { front: "goss-front", back: "goss-back" },
    2: { front: "mage-front", back: "mage-back" },
  },
  pigMonster: {
    1: { front: "pig-front", back: "pig-back" },
    2: { front: "boar-front", back: "boar-back" },
  },
  bookMonster: {
    1: { front: "book-front", back: "book-back" },
    2: { front: "deathnote-front", back: "deathnote-back" },
  },
  dragonMonster: {
    1: { front: "dragon-front", back: "dragon-back" },
  },
  pythonMonster: {
    1: { front: "python-front", back: "python-back" },
  },
  kayouMonster: {
    1: { front: "kayou-front", back: "kayou-back" },
    2: { front: "grokayou-front", back: "grokayou-back" },
    3: { front: "drakayou-front", back: "drakayou-back" },
  },
  tanukiMonster: {
    1: { front: "tanuki-front", back: "tanuki-back" },
  },
  snailMonster: {
    1: { front: "snail-front", back: "snail-back" },
    2: { front: "shell-front", back: "shell-back" },
    3: { front: "pearl-front", back: "pearl-back" },
  },
  ghostMonster: {
    1: { front: "ghost-front", back: "ghost-back" },
    2: { front: "gast-front", back: "gast-back" },
  },
};
